bigwords.com 2011-05-26

# BIGWORDS.com | Buy Textbooks | Sell Textbooks | Cheap Textbooks | Cheapest Textbooks | Compare Textbook Prices | Used College Textbooks | New College Textbooks | Textbook Price Comparison | Textbook Buyback | Textbook Price Bot | New and Used Music | Compare CD Prices | Compare DVD Prices | Compare Video Game Prices | New and Used DVDs | New and Used Video Games

Privacy Statement for BIGGER Words, Inc.

**Privacy**  
Simply stated, we don't sell or trade your information - ever - period - done. If you ever want off our list, use the contact button at the top and bottom of every page, and tell us what you want.

Here's that statement in a more lawyer friendly format.

**BIGWORDS.com Privacy Policy**

**About Us  
**This is a privacy policy for BIGGER Words, Inc.. Our homepage on the Web is located at [ http://www.bigwords.com/](http://www.bigwords.com/). The full text of our privacy policy is available on the Web at [ http://BIGWORDS.com/help/index.php?z=privacy](http://bigwords.com/help/index.php?z=privacy) Users may go to [ http://BIGWORDS.com/help/index.php?z=privacy](http://bigwords.com/help/index.php?z=privacy) for information on how to opt-in or opt-out of use of their information. 

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by mail at the following address: 

    BIGGER Words, Inc.
    171 Pier Ave. #141
    Santa Monica, CA 90405
    US

You may contact us by e-mail at [ bigwords@bigwords.com](mailto:bigwords@bigwords.com). 

**Dispute Resolution and Privacy Seals**   
We have the following privacy seals and/or dispute resolution mechanisms. If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, they can help you resolve your concern. 

  * **New Dispute** : Click on "contact" or "email us" at the top or bottom of this or any page. Tell us the problem, and we will work with you to resolve it promptly. 

**Additional Information**   
This policy is valid for 4 weeks from the time that it is loaded by a client. 

**Data Collection**   
P3P policies declare the data they collect in groups (also referred to as "statements"). This policy contains 2 data groups. The data practices of each group will be explained separately.

**Group "Basic information"**   

We collect the following information: 

  * Click-stream data
  * HTTP protocol elements
  * Search terms

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Completion and support of the current activity.
  * Web site and system administration.
  * Research and development.

This data will be used by ourselves and our agents. 

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:

> Data collected from all Web users: access logs, and search strings (if entered).

**Group "Cookies"**   
We collect the following information: 

  * HTTP cookies

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Research and development.
  * One-time tailoring.
  * Anonymous user analysis.
  * Anonymous user profiling and decision-making.
  * User analysis.
  * User profiling and decision-making.

This data will be used by ourselves and our agents. 

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:

> Cookies are used to track visitors to our site, so we can better understand what portions of our site best serve you.

**Cookies**   
Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. 

Our site makes use of cookies. Cookies are used for the following purposes: 

  * User targeting 
  * Pseudononymous analysis 
  * Pseudonym-based decision-making 
  * User analysis 
  * Individual-based decision-making 
  * Research and development 

**Compact Policy Summary**   
The compact policy which corresponds to this policy is: 

        CP="ALL DSP CURa ADMa DEVa TAIa PSAa PSDa IVAa IVDa OUR BUS IND UNI COM NAV INT STA"

The following table explains the meaning of each field in the compact policy. 

**Field** | **Meaning**  
---|---  
`CP=` | This is the compact policy header; it indicates that what follows is a P3P compact policy.  
`ALL` |  Access to all collected information is available.   
`DSP` |  The policy contains at least one dispute-resolution mechanism.   
`CURa` |  The data is used for completion of the current activity.   
`ADMa` |  The data is used for site administration.   
`DEVa` |  The data is used for research and development.   
`TAIa` |  The data is used for tailoring the site.   
`PSAa` |  The data is used for pseudononymous analysis.   
`PSDa` |  The data is used for pseudononymous decision-making.   
`IVAa` |  The data is used for analysis, including knowledge of the visitor's identity.   
`IVDa` |  The data is used for decision-making, including knowledge of the visitor's identity.   
`OUR` |  The data is given to ourselves and our agents.   
`BUS` |  Our business practices specify how long the data will be kept.   
`IND` |  The data will be kept indefinitely.   
`UNI` |  Unique identifiers are collected.   
`COM` |  Computer information is collected.   
`NAV` |  Navigation and clickstream data is collected.   
`INT` |  Interactive data is collected.   
`STA` |  State-management data is collected   
  
The compact policy is sent by the Web server along with the cookies it describes. For more information, see the P3P deployment guide at <http://www.w3.org/TR/p3pdeployment>. 

© 2011 BIGGER Words, Inc. All rights reserved. Including the right to party.
